<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<section>
	<subnav>
		<item href="services/How can we help" />
		<item href="services/Exhibit Design" />
		<item href="services/Fabrication" />
		<item href="services/Custom Fabrication" />
		<item href="services/Scenic Environments & Events" />
		<item href="services/Mobile Exhibits & Events" />
		<item href="services/Custom Rentals" />
		<item href="services/Graphics" />
		<item href="services/Installation & Project Management" />
		<item href="services/Inventory & Transportation" />
		<item href="services/Technology" />
		<item href="services/Awards" />
	</subnav>
    <content>
	
        <item href="services/How can we help">
        	<title>How we can help!</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Join an award winning team of exhibit, event and environmental designers, fabricators, producers and planners.<br><br>You tell us how we can help plan a profitable experience with accurate, precise and continuous coordination and execution.<br><br>Your success is our success. Let us take care of the details while you enjoy the show!<br>]]></description>
        </item>
		<item href="services/Exhibit Design">
			<title>Exhibit Design</title>
			<description>Our exhibit design process is one of collaboration. It revolves, first and foremost, around research, learning and understanding. Learning as much as possible about our potential clients, existing affiliated agencies, strategies, culture, products, markets and their clients. Our award winning Design Team, Account Managers and Project Managers work interactively with our clients and agency partners, through every step of the development of each program so that all expectations and needs are met at every step from the first initial concept to the final completed product.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Fabrication">
			<title>Fabrication</title>
			<description>Our production facility is state-of-the-art and staffed by some of the finest craftsmen in the industry. Our commitment to quality and to cost effective fabrication and refurbishment has encouraged us to research and invest in the highest level of computer aided manufacturing equipment.

Our fabrication services include:

    * Detailed Millwork
    * Engineering detailing/CAD drawing development
    * Metal Fabrication
    * Paint services
    * Electrical design and fabrication
    * Tensioned Fabric Structures</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Custom Fabrication">
			<title>Custom Fabrication</title>
			<description>Aluminum Fabrication - The Oz System
This versatile aluminum system provides components and fasteners that combine the aesthetic and structural strength ideal for constructing small kiosks and workstations to multi story pavilions and structures.
Manfred Frank ASC Acrylic Showcase System
Winner of the Innovation and Design Award at the SITEM in Paris in 1999, ASC is an easy-to-use, slide-on frame system satisfying the most demanding design and quality requirements. A proven product in museums, professional presentation centers, or as custom exhibit components, these showcases include acrylic panels and fine aluminum profile strips making them highly stable, completely air-tight, and dust-free.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Scenic Environments & Events">
			<title>Scenic Environments & Events</title>
			<description>Fabric Architecture
One of the most popular materials in events, tensioned fabric structures offer the advantages of being lightweight, compact and an ideal material to define large spaces. Our in-house fabric department can create the most complex of custom forms in a variety of materials from spandex to lightweight scrim to waterproof, transparent and printable fabric.
Themed Environments
Our teams of artists and production designers make any themed environment possible. With years of experience in the creation of custom elements for tradeshows, theatre productions, retail environments, museums and casinos, we can tackle any challenge and provide options to suit any design requirement.
Theatres & Staging
Taking care of client requirements, from liaising with show management to developing staging, to hosting hospitality events to arranging giveaways and booking performances, The Taylor Group professionals work with clients to ensure that the event runs smoothly and exceeds expectations.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Mobile Exhibits & Events">
			<title>Mobile Exhibits & Events</title>
			<description>With services ranging from strategy assistance to vehicle design and construction, clients can rely on us to produce quality mobile marketing environments on time and within budget. Our mobile marketing services include interior design, vehicle refurbishing, site selection, event management, tour logistics, field staffing, and mobile marketing program management.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Custom Rentals">
			<title>Custom Rentals</title>
			<description>In this changing economy, our Custom Rental Program can allow you to cut costs while still developing new business and meeting your corporate goals and objectives. Our rental solutions will assist you in creating a quality environment that will convey your message, motivate your audience, and deliver results.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Graphics">
			<title>Graphics</title>
			<description>Our full service in-house graphic production capabilities guarantee the highest quality fastest turn around time for any project. We provide desktop publishing and image setting on PC and MAC platforms, computer-controlled cut vinyl, dimensional graphics, full-colour inkjet printing on numerous substrates (including fabric), as well as any other processes that suite the design and requirements.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Installation & Project Management">
			<title>Installation & Project Management</title>
			<description>Installation & Dismantle
The Taylor Group offers a full staff of internal site supervisors who travel to each location and where possible remain with select client programs in order to promote familiarity and site associated cost savings.
Project Management
At the outset of each project the Project Manager provides a scheduling document outlining all relevant milestones including progress and budget updates. Quality control, design and production status is monitored using project management software. All project documentation is readily available during each phase of any program for inspection. We encourage tours of our facility at your convenience for in-person progress reviews during pre-show set up.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Inventory & Transportation">
			<title>Inventory & Transportation</title>
			<description>Inventory Management
Our inventory management process includes the tracking of all exhibit components by catalogue identification number and crate labeling. This process ensures easy location of elements while allowing for efficient and expedient loading and off-loading.
All warehouse facilities are climate controlled and are insured for fire, theft and damage. A secure lockdown area is also utilized for storage of strategically sensitive or valuable merchandise.
Transportation
At The Taylor Group we have our own transportation services, as well as strong and reliable relationships with various cost effective independent carriers. Combined with our competitive costs, accessibility to all major North American centers and direct-to-site service, this ensures safe, timely and cost effective transportation. In addition, we secure all customs brokerage and duties.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Technology">
			<title>Technology</title>
			<description>
To enhance our communication ability, Taylor developed TWIST: Taylor Worldwide Information System Technology. This secure, on-line utility provides our clients with 24-hour access to The Taylor Group and is included in every client program.

Additionally The Taylor Group provides various interactive options for all exhibit, event or experience environments, including the latest in digital signage, web enabled applications and RFID technology.</description>
		</item>
		<item href="services/Awards">
			<title>Awards</title>
			<description>Readers Choice, Best Exhibit in 20 years
Teknion Furniture Systems: IIDEX Show, NeoCon Canada, Exhibitor Magazine, 2006
Design: Burdifilek, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Silver Award, Exhibit Design
Electronic Entertainment Expo Exhibit - Lounge: Xbox Exhibit, E3 Show, California
Exhibitor Magazine, 2006
Design: Purepartner by Design, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Merit Award, Exhibit Design
Electronic Entertainment Expo Exhibit - Specialty Area: Xbox Exhibit, E3 Show, California
Exhibitor Magazine, 2006
Design: Purepartner by Design, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Silver Award, Exhibit Design
Intel: Geneva Telecom Show, Switzerland, Exhibitor Magazine, 2003
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Exhibit Design, Award of Merit
Teknion Furniture Systems: IIDEX Show, NeoCon Canada, Exhibitor Magazine, 2003
Design: Burdifilek, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Exhibit Design, Special Merit Award(for Double-Deck exhibits less than $150 / sq.ft.)
GMR Marketing, Microsoft Xbox: E3 Show, California, Exhibitor Magazine, 2003
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Exhibit Design, Silver Award(for Double-Deck exhibits less than $150 / sq.ft.)
GMR Marketing, Microsoft Xbox: E3 Show, Los Angeles, California, Exhibitor Magazine, 2002
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Exhibit Design, Edge Award(for Island exhibits less than $150 / sq.ft.)
Teknion Furniture Systems: IIDEX Show, NeoCon Canada, Exhibitor Magazine, 2002
Design: Burdifilek, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

The Business Events Guide Exhibit Excellence Award (for exhibits under 240 sq.ft.)
Zero Knowledge, Toronto, Canada, Exhibit & Display Association of Canada, 2000
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Icon Digital Productions Award of Excellence(for Special Projects under $100,000)
Manitoba Lotteries, Club Regent, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada
Exhibit & Display Association of Canada, 1999

Business Excellence Awards - Growth
The Taylor Group, Brampton, Ontario, Canada (previously located in Etobicoke, Ontario)
Etobicoke Chamber of Commerce, 1998

Octanorm President's Award of Excellence(for exhibits under 240 sq.ft.)
The Taylor Group, Brampton, Ontario, Canada
Exhibit & Display Association of Canada, 1997

Strategy Award of Exhibit Excellence (for Special Projects over $100 000)
Royal Bank of Canada, Vancouver Int'l Airport,
Canada, Exhibit & Display Assoc. of Canada, 1997
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Award of Exhibit Excellence(for exhibits over 60 / sq.ft.)
ADAC Technologies: Lange Transportation & Storage Show
Exhibit & Display Assoc. of Canada, 1997
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group

Best Exhibit(for exhibits over 200 sq.ft. or more)
Rogers Cable Systems Ltd., Property Management Expo & Conference, 1996
Design: The Taylor Group, Fabrication: The Taylor Group </description>
		</item>
    </content>
</section>